Hi everyone, it's a new video. It's kind of like every time I say the same, but I don't know. I
don't know anything else to say. So hi, this is another jumpsuit up video. Can we please take a
moment to appreciate how good my hair looks together with the blue dress here? Sorry.
Back to topic. Jumpsuit up! So I have another see-through jumpsuit today. You may have seen
the Demo-Nique try on video and this is another Demo-Nique piece although it's from a different
collection therefore you see it here. It is a very special fabric I'm going to tell you more about it
once I'm wearing it. So it's super special but first I'm going to change into it.
Tada! What do you think? How do you like it? I am not used to so much see-through fabric but it is
really cool. The model on product picture is wearing rather plain underwear with a bandeau
and some panties and I decided to go with a more fanciful, fanciful Dessus set. So
I think it pulls the look even a bit more together and it makes, I don't know, it looks a bit more
playful so to say. And you have to take a look at the back side. Okay but as I already said there
are some specialties here. This fabric is called or this line rather is called
silver thread. So it is a silver thread running through the whole garment. That's
why it sparkles so much. But on the other hand it is not really stretchy due to
that silver thread and it is not really skin tight here. So these are a few
things you have to know about this fabric. If you're fine with that then
this is a really cool outfit and you can wear to I don't know parties or just at
home whatever. I really like the sparkling look so I'm kind of a fan but
it is its own look. I combined this jumpsuit with some killer heels and yeah
some riveted heels so I think it is an extra touch to the look and yeah I think
they have other items with this silver thread line just check out their
homepage I'll link everything down below I hope you enjoyed this video as always
and see you next time bye
Thank you.